<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<PrayerRequests>
  <Entry>
    <Category />
    <Type />
    <Text />
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>IOUS</Category>
    <Type>Pray for IOUS</Type>
    <Text>&lt;B&gt;Inclination toward God and His word&lt;/B&gt; - Ps 119:36 - "Incline my heart to your testimonies, and not to selfish gain!" &lt;B&gt;Opened eyes&lt;/B&gt; - Psalm 119:18 - "Open my eyes, that I may behold wondrous things out of your law." &lt;B&gt;United heart&lt;/B&gt; - Psalm 86:11 - "Teach me your way, O LORD, that I may walk in your truth; unite my heart to fear your name." &lt;B&gt;Satisfaction in the Lord&lt;/B&gt; - Psalm 90:14 - "Satisfy us in the morning with your steadfast love, that we may rejoice and be glad all our days."
		</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>FederalGovernment</Category>
    <Type>Federal Government</Type>
    <Text>"The king's heart is in the hand of the LORD; he directs it like a watercourse wherever he pleases." (Proverbs 21:1) President Bush, Vice-President Cheney, Cabinet, Dept. Heads, Advisors, Military Leaders and all personnel, Senate, House of Representatives, Supreme Court, Federal Courts.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>StateGovernment</Category>
    <Type>State Government</Type>
    <Text>Govenors, Legislature, State Courts, State Militia, Law Enforcement.		</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>LocalGovernment</Category>
    <Type>Local Government</Type>
    <Text>City Managers, Council Members, Mayors, Police, Sheriff and Deputies, Local Courts.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>ImmediateFamily</Category>
    <Type>Immediate Family</Type>
    <Text>Jackie - health, safety, wellbeing, blessing from You, and joy. For strength for dealing with the various systems for Seth and John, for working as a sales rep and with Johnny and Fran. That I be the husband that I should be to her. Seth - his salvation; "No one can come to me unless the Father who sent me draws him. And I will raise him up on the last day." John 6:44; John - his goals be Biblically motivated. That he make proper selections in what he hears and views. Motivation for him to do all these things as well.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>ExtendedFamily</Category>
    <Type>Extended Family</Type>
    <Text>Mom and Jim; Jesse, Josh, and Cheryl; Dale, Dustin, Danita, Erin; Doug, Garrett, and Benjamin; Rusty, Debbie and Jared; Chris, Tim, and Erin; Lori, her husband, CJ, Carli; Tim, Zach, Tiff, Timmy; Mimi, Sharon, Eric, Tiffany, Kirsten and Family; Becky, Cheryl, Steve, Henrietta, Bob and families; Ed, Barb, Rod, Mary Dawn, Scott, Buffy, Tyler, Tanner, Christy; Bruce, Betsy, Jonathon; Amanda, Donna, Holly, Scott, Craig, and families.	</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>WorldSituation</Category>
    <Type>World Situation</Type>
    <Text>Stop the killing. Protection for our troops, frustration of the enemies, God's ultimate will to be done in Iraq and indeed around the world. Help the Iraq government be setup smoothly. That the Iraqi government setup and use their own security forces. God's will in the up coming state and local elections.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>Coworkers</Category>
    <Type>Coworkers</Type>
    <Text>For the coworkers and environment at US Bank. I need to be a light there. I pray for Brian Lewis, Norma, Jason, Reed, Kate, Sarah, Howard, Allison, Marilyn, Mike Huston, John, Doug, Pete, Jim, Dean, Daryl, Rob, Gregg, Matt, Brian Harwell, Chris S., Sean, and Jeff. Also Rob Cheek's team - Rob C., Teresa, John, Rob H., Padma, Brian Harvey, new personel, and contractors. God's will done in their lives. Harmony at work, but not at the cost of your truth Lord.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>Skills</Category>
    <Type>Skills</Type>
    <Text>But seek first his kingdom and his righteousness, and all these things will be given to you as well. (Matt. 6:33) Give me proper motivation for skills, life, Biblical, and professional, and the ability to get the skills. Balanced study according to Your will Lord.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>ChurchStaff</Category>
    <Type>Church Staff</Type>
    <Text>Pastor Brad and his family, Pastor Steve and family, David Clegg and his family, Pastor Bob and his family, Elders and families, Deacons and families, Sunday School Teachers, Worship Team, for the small groups. Your will done there God.
		</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>Neighbors</Category>
    <Type>Neighbors</Type>
    <Text>Lonnie and family; Bee; Teresa, Fran and Johnny; the Cullum Family and their situation, and family; Jack and his wife; Diane and husband; George and wife; Moynahan Family; Gary, Virgina, and family; Fransqua and family. I pray for the salvation, earthly wellbeing and our harmony with them in the neighborhood.
		</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>Individuals</Category>
    <Type>Individuals</Type>
    <Text>Bee and Teresa and their relationships. Rachel, the burn victim for healing and family help. Don and Jeanne Bowdle. For Blake Dinger who is in Pure Life now.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>Me</Category>
    <Type>Me</Type>
    <Text>Guard me from results such as Proverbs 14:12 - "There is a way that seems right to a man, but in the end it leads to death." Lord, lead and guide me in every way. And to be mindful of Proverbs 19:21 - "Many are the plans in a man's heart, but it is the LORD's purpose that prevails." Lord help me to maintain a Biblical worldview governed by a realization of your act of creation, our act of the fall, and your redemption. Help me to be the father and husband that I should be. </Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>Missionary</Category>
    <Type>Missionary Weekly Requests</Type>
    <Text>This week we will turn our prayers toward Dave and Carrie who are working in Southeast Asia.

 

Monday: Praise God that Carrie and David have found a house to move to since their landlord is selling the one they live in now.  Pray that the final negotiations will go well and that a contract for at least two years will be able to be signed in a timely manner.

 

Tuesday:  Pray that all the details of their move will go smoothly and that they would be able to move into their new location by April 1st.  Pray that through the move they would be able to maintain their focus on their work.  Pray for new relationships with their new neighbors and continued development of relationships with their current neighbors.  Pray that the gift of faith and repentance would be granted in several of their current relationships as well as in new relationships as a result of the move.

 

Wednesday: Pray for Carrie and David and their efforts to learn the language.  At times it seems tedious and they often feel that they will never learn to speak properly.  Pray that God would give them special grace to hear and speak the language well.

 

Thursday:  Pray for Kobe and Grant and their schooling.  Grant is attending a public Muslim school where there is no English spoken.  Pray for protection and pray that Grant would be able to learn the language quickly.  Kobe’s school does use English so pray that he would grow in knowledge of the culture but yet also be able to see the need for Christ in his life.  Pray for the English camp that the GFC team is planning for the summer.  Pray that many new contacts would result from this effort

 

Friday:  Pray for the full time Muslim housekeeper that will begin living with Carrie and David soon.  The housekeeper speaks no English so pray that Carrie and David will be able to learn to communicate with her and that this arrangement would give them insights into the Muslim worldview.  (This is a typical household arrangement which will allow Carrie greater ministry freedom and also offer a wonderful opportunity to “live Christ.”

 

Saturday:  Pray for David and his efforts to establish contacts with Muslims through the business efforts he is involved with.  Pray for the small fellowship that Carrie and David have been attending.  Pray that they will have a common purpose and that cultural barriers would not inhibit the flow of love amongst the attenders of this fellowship.

 

Sunday:  Pray for the entire group of US citizens living in nearly the same circumstances as Carrie and David.  Pray for a unity and an increased level of ministering to one another.  Pray for the VBS that the GFC team will help conduct later this summer.  Pray specifically for Carrie, David, Grant and Kobe’s safety as well as for boldness.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Category>SmallGroup</Category>
    <Type>Small Group</Type>
    <Text>Bill and Joan and family; Ron and Judy Schrader and family; Scott and Linda Brumback</Text>
  </Entry>
</PrayerRequests>