<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<PrayerJournal>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/7/2006 10:33:57 AM</Date>
    <Text>The small group is starting to have a monthly memory verse. It was exciting to hear everyone speak of the struggles that they have in being consistent in daily prayers and bible reading.One thing of note is this month's verses, Eph. 4:22-24 (NIV) which starts "And you were taught, with regard to your former way of life, to put off the old self, which is being corrupted by its deceitful desires, and to be made new in the attitudes of your minds, and to put on the new self, created to be like God in true rightousness and holiness." Note that even as believers, we have to put off the old, which be the way is actively being corrupted by deceitful desires, now, and to be renewed in our thinking. That is, be aware of what the default way we think, currupted!! And by the Holy Spirit's help change the thinking.
</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>12/30/2005 10:04:09 AM</Date>
    <Text>Ps 119:36 - "Incline my heart to your testimonies, and not to selfish gain!" The very fact of this contrast means that I am not do not naturally desire God's Word, but rather what is of interest to me and my advancement. Therefore, it takes the Holy Spirit to change that. As I understand, this is done by reading and meditating on the word.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>12/29/2005 10:09:06 AM</Date>
    <Text>Psalm 119:18 - "Open my eyes, that I may behold wondrous things out of your law." Therefore, the wonderous things are there. By God's grace they will be unvailed to me. I will make a few goals for this coming year. I need a structured Bible reading plan. I think chronological is good but I need to focus in on the New Testement this year. At least I think so now. We will see. In any event I will place the goals on my yahoo calendar and set markers as I go on the calendar.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>12/14/2005 6:06:25 AM</Date>
    <Text>It is interesting to note that when I focus on prayer and meditate on the word of God, I am clearer in my thinking and therefore can plan, work, and function better. Speaking of that I need to look at the end Exodus. Moreover, I need to look at how I can see direct application. As with all the word of God, it is there to be found.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>12/13/2005 5:54:09 AM</Date>
    <Text>Last night was the Small Group Leaders meeting. One point that was raised in discussion was that you need to apply God's word in an action that is measurable and concrete. I am commiting to 3 weeks of at least 20 minutes of prayer and meditation each morning before leaving the house.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>12/12/2005 6:07:46 AM</Date>
    <Text>About time I get started in adding more to the journal. This could be something that I add to throughout the day via edits to the entry. One thing I need to do and pray about is being sensative to what and how I say things.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>3/28/2005 1:54:46 PM</Date>
    <Text>I was thinking of a couple BLOG ideas: 1. discussing the "great denial" that many are in. The thought is from John Piper's analogy of the Titanic and those aboard to continue mery making if they knew they were heading toward the iceberg. How foolish it would be to do that knowing of impending doom. And why would they do that? They do not believe the warning from the lookout? The second is a discussion of the mental makeup of a liberal and conservative from a fallen perspective. In other words, what in our sinful nature would make liberalism attaractive (define your own rules, open sex, etc) and what would make conservatism attractive (greed if you are wealthy, traditional power strucures if you are in the structure, etc). Then review perhaps why believers are a mix of views (liberal with help conservative on values of life).</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>2/28/2005 6:05:19 AM</Date>
    <Text>Had a blessed weekend up at the Worldview Conference at Grace Community in Washington CH this weekend. I have much reading and prayer to do as the result!</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>2/15/2005 9:27:36 PM</Date>
    <Text>Gave the default page a face lift with a style sheet and Joshua's mens memory vserses. Lord help me to meditate on the scriptures I see on the site.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>2/9/2005 7:01:24 AM</Date>
    <Text>Picked up the truck last night. Lord help us with our vehicles as I am no mechanic. Help me be focused on work and in serving you. Seth is apptitude testing today and tomorrow, help him with that. Tahnk you Lord for the opportunities. Guide me in the way I should go. Because most of the time, I do not know for certain the specifics.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>2/8/2005 5:56:18 AM</Date>
    <Text>I am now mobile on the prayer journal as it is now on my website. Now I can access it anywhere I have internet access!! I am picking up the new truck today. We are not getting the warranty as the low milage on the truck and what appears to be good shape have discouraged that. We will continue with the financial plan to get out of debt. Lord help us in all these matters. Also, I am needing more focus with Account Recon and the rewriting of the Waivers section. God, you who created the mind can help. I thank you for what help you give as I do not deserve anything you do for me.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>2/7/2005 7:02:17 AM</Date>
    <Text>Concerning the cares of this life and my work, I need to trust God in these matters, do the work, and allow Him to move on me and the circumstances and leave it in His hands. Lord also guide us in the matters of the truck and the financing.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>2/6/2005 3:17:49 PM</Date>
    <Text>I am now using the sorted prayer journal. This will be more useful as the new entries are at the top. I must do what Pastor Steve said in using the journal to write thoughts on passages. I will need to copy this project to my jump drive or even better to my website.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/23/2005 6:30:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I think the best place for my ideas are in here. Since I need to pray, I can place prayers, ideas, and lists here.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>12/5/2004 6:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I am thinking of writing a list of ideas about articles. I will keep that in Word or may place in this journal during prayer time.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>8/19/2004 7:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>John had his "meet the team" dinner last night. I am thankful that he sat with me. Jackie stated that he does not get along with the upperclassman as well as he wished. Lord help us all to understand and know that we will not please everyone and be appealing to all. Therefore, and even if we could please all men, may we be pleasing to you. That is all that matters.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>8/18/2004 6:20:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Had a good first accountability with Derick last night at Applebees. I am looking forward to spending those times with him as we discuss the word and pray for one another.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>8/16/2004 6:15:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Last Friday I spent some time at MLTs with some guys from work. Usually I enjoy the short time there talking. But this time, the language and topic of conversation was unreserved on some that were there. That is it. I myself was not set apart enough and that was my fault. God help me that this will not and never happen again.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>8/11/2004 6:25:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Having our first meeting with the Use Cases for the rewrite of ERM. Lord help me to take the proper steps in the project at the proper time. </Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>8/10/2004 6:45:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>This is the first time using the journal within the web tool. As you can see it has been awhile since the last entry. Since this is more interactive, I trust I will use it more.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>2/10/2004 6:20:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Up early this morning. One thing that never changes is the need for the Lord to provide us wisdom and understanding! Give Jackie and I financial wisdom.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>2/2/2004 6:10:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I need to trust the Lord more when it comes to my side business. He can and will supply the needs!!</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/29/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Training has been going well this week. Most of the concepts I have been over before here at home but review is good. Jackie and I had a good discussion about the QC website. I have started to improve the admin side of it. Will need to factor out some methods to put into a base class and add some functionality such as select a category from a drop down menu in main datagrid and edit the categories in another screen.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/27/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I am in training downtown this week. The routine has changed and is odd but I thank God that I can learn new things on the job. Lord help me prepare for the Sunday School class throughout the week.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/23/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Lee, Jesse's ex-wife passed away yesterday. We are going up this evening to the calling in Mt. Sterling. I pray the trip and all goes well. I pray for Doug, Josh, and Moose.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/22/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I need to get with the Lord in the evening and seek His guidance and fellowship. God help me in this.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/21/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I had to work later last night as the PCGIT project is coming to a build for IT. The projects will only go into UAT as far as I know. In any event, Lord give me wisdom to do Your will and to do the job that you have given me.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/20/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I am considering moving back to the NIV or ESV for reading and use the Message for clarification at times needed. With it available online I am not sure I want to spend the $30 to buy it.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/19/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I had a good weekend concerning events. The ski trip was canceled due to freezing rain in the area. The boys are off today, which is Monday, and tomorrow. I hope to finish up this defect with this VB 6 class and the surrounding code. </Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/16/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I am thankful this is Friday. And I am learning a good deal about COM.I hope that Seth will want to hang with me on the ski trip tomorrow. And that the trip will not be too far to the resort.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/15/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I know that Seth is ready for the classroom and to get out of the room that he has been in for the past month there in school. Lord help hom and all of us throughout the day.Help John have decernment. Help Jackie physically and with energy.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/14/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Monday the 12th the boys helped Jackie with the Wicker kids. I was glad for that and promised them we could go see a movie Tuesday. I forgot that Tuesday was Youth Group night at the church. Yet, because I promised Seth wanted to go and was looking forward to it. With God's help I will now encourage the boys to go to Tuesday night youth group as it is the right thing to do.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/13/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Had a good parent meeting at the church last night with pastor John. His vision for the ministry is good.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/12/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>Had a good weekend. It appears that Jackie is fearful concerning the new business ventures. I will need to take a more active role perhaps. Lord, you will done in this.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/9/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>May prayer is still that God would bring an end to the terrorist activities against our soldiers. In fact, to stop them, frustrate them. May their own weapons be used against them. Yes, that they come to know the truth. Yet, God's will done.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/8/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I had a good discussion with the boys last night at devotion time on the Job and suffering. I read the intro for the book of Job from the Message paraphrase. We discussed the use of suffering and how that when you serve God you will not suffer less often, but more.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/7/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I need to be more selective on the tasks that I spend my time on. Some things I do are not very productive. I need to ask myself, "What is that I can do that would be most productive concerning this or that?" Of course fellowship with Gos is number one!!! Other things do not apply.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/6/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>God help us in deal with our children and help them to recieve the instruction. Help me with he reports. Give me incite and motivation. To You be ALL praise!!</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/5/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>I noted as I got down on my knees and was praying how that my mond was wondering and thinking of times in high shcool that at least it appeared that the girls found me attaractive. Why did my mind think that way? Beacause I am sinful and vain and self deceived left to myself. God help me in this new year. I have written down some goals but must get them into plans if you are willing.</Text>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Date>1/4/2004 12:00:00 AM</Date>
    <Text>This is the first morning in the new church building for Grace Fellowship. There is no Sunday School this morning. After church is a potluck at the new home of the Servants. I have been praying for direction concerning education and entrepenural ventures as we need God's guidance. This way Jackie will not have to work a waitress job etc. Thinking of God's grace as we traveled to Oneida, on Dec. 6th, leaving at 12:30 AM, getting there at 4:30 AM, getting home at 7:30 AM, and talking with Seth that morning, and finally depending on God's grace for the outcomes.  </Text>
  </Entry>
</PrayerJournal>